16 YEARS AGO
Our VIP and his family are in the suite.
There are also three rebels. Extract the VIP and family.
If you can't, we're going in.
Copy that.
Hands up.
Get out.
There are far more hostages than we anticipated,
Including Koreans and other nationalities.
The operation is too much of a risk.
Concentrate on extracting the VIP. He's our top priority.
It's not safe.
Some of the hostages are disguised as terrorists.
Are you certain?
We can't delay this operation any longer based on unconfirmed information.
Taking down five terrorists isn't a problem for us.
Don't you agree?
Let's go.
Move in.
You can't. It's too dangerous.
We need to act before there are more casualties.
Move in.
J, don't go! Don't do it!
- We're moving in. -  I said no!
Stay here. I'll come back.
I remember.
Jeong Jinman.
SIGMA CONFIDENTIAL PROFILE
My hotel is just around the corner.
My schedule is a bit tight.
- Wanna stop? - No, please, do continue.
Tight is good!
There's a Russian saying.
Live like you're friends with the bear.
But hold onto an ax.
I have never met a Japanese woman who knows a Russian proverb.
I like bears.
They are wild. :cue
But cute.
Like you, Dimitri.
You shouldn't steal from Babylon
Dimitri.
You fucking bitch!
Is the drug working?
-  The DJ isn't great tonight. -  Agreed.
Give me your lipstick.
What's that noise? A guy?
Get a hotel room!
Why? I like doing it here too.
What?
Seriously?
No, for real. What are they doing in there?
This is the women's restroom.
All good, I took him out.
Get someone over here to clean this up.
The director said to get back to the team ASAP.
Mm-hmm. Yeah, okay.
CONFIDENTIAL PROFILE PERSONAL PROFILE NAME JEONG JINMAN
CONFIDENTIAL PROFILE PERSONAL PROFILE NAME JEONG JIAN
JEONG JI-AN
Jian?
The operation's a failure!
Rescuing the hostage is the top priority.
Why did you jump out in front when you're the team leader?
While you were busy playing the hero,
Your team was wiped out.
Hey, by the way, why'd you make this guy the hostage?
Wasn't it supposed to be a little kid?
L.
How come you didn't rescue M?
Sorry, Q killed me.
Oneechan.
Not fair.
Why'd you come? You weren't supposed to be part of this operation.
Hm As the leader, you should always be prepared, right?
Wow. Good one.
We have a new mission.
J.
L, M.
X. Marco.
Be at Kansai Airport by 9:00 a.m. tomorrow.
The operations brief will begin once we arrive.
Let me know if you need personal firearms. I'll send them through my company.
Where's the operation area?
Korea.
A SHOP FOR KILLERS 2
EPISODE 03 PAST IS PAST, PRESENT IS PRESENT :cue
MURTHEHELP
We've been getting a lot of reports lately about smuggling.
Smuggling what?
Why would anybody wanna smuggle something here?
I'm done with the search. Nothing here.
All right, let's head home.
Yes, sir.
Oh. Is that the girlfriend the ladies were talking about?
Oh! A midnight date?
What girlfriend? Have a good night.
- Nice to meet you, miss! - Time to go home, please.
Woojin is finally getting married, huh?
Goodbye.
Miss Arin.
Arin.
MURTHEHELP
MURTHEHELP SEARCH
BROTHER JEONG JINMAN MASTER PASIN
Uh, Miss Arin.
- Can I explain what happened? - That won't be necessary.
I'm not interested.
- Still, I-- - I said I don't care.
I'm not even curious about it.
Right.
Sorry about that.
Jian, do you think running away is gonna change anything? Hm?
What am I supposed to do?
Jeong Jian, from now on, you have to stay alive on your own.
This bag here, just once you get somewhere safe.
Open it when you're alone.
READ CAREFULLY JEONG JIAN :cue
What did Jeong Jinman do for them to call us all the way here?
You took someone out in Korea didn't you?
Yeah.
During the exhausting day-trip boat mission.
That guy was Jeong Jinman's old boss.
It seems like Jeong Jinman has decided to become a traitor.
Interesting.
They forced him out of the company.
This is karma.
What?
- What do you mean? - Think about it.
You told Babylon about Jeong Jinman. Said to recruit him.
But now, here we are coming to Korea to capture him.
Definitely karma.
Hey. If Jeong Jinman wasn't there, you definitely would've died.
The past is the past, and the present is the present.
Oh. Is that the place?
Stay here. I'll come back.
STAFF ONLY
Stay there!
Just sit down, sit down!
- How many are there? -  Two dead, three remaining.
Two in front of the door, one inside the room.
Jun.
Jun!
Bang!
Shut up, shut up!
We're from Korea. Don't be scared.
Put the gun down. Or she will die.
- Drop the gun. - Help me!
I said drop it!
I have a child. Please!
Please let me go!
Please!
No. Please.
:cue
- Make way, make way. - Thanks for saving us.
Yes, sir, I'm taking the hostages now.
- Our pleasure. - Mm-hmm. Thank you.
You'll be assisted back home by the embassy.
That's what you get for not listening to me.
What else was I supposed to do?
You gotta stand down when I tell you not to move in!
You'll get yourself into hot water if you keep being so reckless.
- J, are you okay? - Yeah, I'm fine.
Kusanagi Jin. Team leader of Babylon.
Nobody goes harder than you.
Jinman Jeong, Master Sergeant of Korean Special Forces.
Business as usual, right?
It would've been nice if Korean Forces had informed us.
It caused us confusion in our operation, and we almost lost the mission.
Are you Korean?
Something like that.
-  Yeah, it's cute. - Wanna wear it?
- No, thanks. - Try it on.
Hey, J, maybe you should've worn it instead of Q.
Hard to say. Without confirming with our Special Forces beforehand,
Rushing in could've harmed the foreign hostages.
What?
Please take over for me.
What? Uh, Jinman where are you going?
Let's go!
I didn't get to introduce myself. Q is what they call me.
I'm Jeong Jinman.
Your Korean is good.
Ah, I have a Korean friend in Osaka.
-  I've been studying. -  Oh, I see.
The operation was classified, so I couldn't say anything.
-  I'm sorry. -  I understand.
Is that him? The person who saved me?
Thank you.
I'll come back to work right away.
Don't come to the hospital. It's a hassle.
- I'll be there later, so behave yourself. -  What?
That hurts.
Uh I, um
I really appreciate what you did.
Would you like to get a drink?
The drink is on me.
We'll be leaving the country in a few hours.
It was an unofficial operation.
Ah
Okay.
- Then, um, then have a safe flight. - You did a good job.
You're just gonna leave like that?
Excuse me.
Yes?
The next time we meet, we'll go have a drink together.
Either in Japan or Korea.
:cue
Hello.
I look forward to your kind operation. Thank you.
Hey. They'll think we're pushovers if you do that.
I'm just honey trapping to help lower their guard a little.
How are you honey trapping without any honey?
Hey. Don't forget, just because we're here,
Doesn't mean that we should be bulldogs.
Leadership isn't coerced. It's something you have to earn.
Nice to meet you.
Oh, shit
Gross.
Why does it smell musty?
I know it's not ideal.
This is our accommodation.
Make the best of it.
Somebody's in there.
You're the ones?
You came all the way across the sea to capture Jeong Jinman?
Hello.
I'm Q. The team lead.
A woman?
Hey, one-eye.
I don't have to know what you're saying
To understand that your tone is damn cocky.
It's unbelievable.
They made off with the entire server
And nothing's happened yet?
That's really weird.
All the confidential data on the server is encrypted.
Just because Jeong Jinman has the server,
Doesn't mean he'll be able to un-encrypt it.
Either Jinman hasn't cracked the code
Or he's honoring the agreement to ceasefire.
Jeong Jinman made that promise on his own.
The company won't consider tolerating even a one percent risk.
What's the status of progress?
This.
Jeong Jinman's website is currently under construction.
We are using his own system against him, and developed a murthehelp app in secret.
Think of it as a secondhand marketplace for weapons.
Jeong Jinman controlled everything on the website,
But the app operates as more of an open marketplace.
As the number of users grow, the data grows with it.
On the surface level, this app appears to have no relationship with Babylon.
- Jeong Jinman's niece? -  Correct.
Jeong Jian.
Jinman's only Achilles' heel.
Once the number of users exceed a certain threshold,
We plan to put a bounty on Jeong Jian.
When we capture the kid, Jinman will come out from the shadows.
While trying to capture her last year, two entire teams were wiped out.
One of which was Babylon's main unit.
- His associates? -  That's right.
If we start by cutting off the legs, the right arm, then the left :cue
We can focus on cutting off the head.
Then we'll be able to recover the server from Jeong Jinman
And we'll have eliminated them all.
What about that one-eyed asshole from earlier?
Bale? Did you say hello?
- Do we really have to work with him? -  Why not?
Are you scared?
I'm not scared.
I'm worried he'll get in the way.
What do you think, Q?
DOWNLOAD M MURTHEHELP
WOULD YOU LIKE TO DOWNLOAD MURTHEHELP.APK FILE?
DOWNLOAD MURTHEHELP.APK 0%
It looks the same.
Except it's missing code green.
THIS IS MURTHEHELP APP WHAT IS IT?
WOOJIN
I thought something exploded. Why are you so late?
- Let's move them, hurry. - Well
Something happened along the way.
The waves were rough when we were crossing the Chinese borders.
What do we do? She's losing a lot of blood.
- We need to get her to the hospital. - We can't do that.
We're doing something illegal. If we get caught, we'll both go to prison.
I don't want to go back to jail.
I'd rather be dead than go back there.
Just pretend you don't know.
How could I do that? You just want to leave her to die?
Let's just push her over the edge.
Nobody has to know about this.
I can't believe you just said that!
Shit.
Hey.
I'll just say I did everything.
Keep your hands clean. All right?
I'll turn myself in after I take her to the hospital.
Take the others to their parents, and do it right.
You can't.
I'm sorry. I have no other choice but to do this.
Miss Arin. :cue
Miss Arin, you're using a fishing hook.
Did you go to med school?
It's better than dying.
We have to do something.
Oh, my baby, my baby. Mommy's here.
I missed you so much. Are you all right?
We treated her, but make sure you take her to the hospital.
I understand, I will.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay. It's Mommy.
Here, take this.
She needs a doctor.
Thank you so much.
Sorry. Sorry.
-  I'm so sorry. -  No. Thank you.
MURTHEHELP APP ISN'T OURS. WE'RE TRACKING IT NOW. BE CAREFUL. BROTHER
It's okay, it's okay.
When they come to Korea,
They can get a work visa, but it's only for them.
They can't bring their children.
That's why sometimes, I smuggle the kids in.
I take them to their parents in Korea.
That's what I was doing.
What about the other night?
Those were guns, right?
Well, that guy, the one that you knocked out, asked for a favor.
I never in a million years thought they could be guns.
I think that tomorrow, I'll go to the police and turn myself in.
Don't worry about anything.
Tell me what this is.
MURTHEHELP
Nice to meet you all.
Hi, there. I'm still getting used to this location.
It's a pleasure.
- Looking forward to it. - Thank you.
Please enjoy while you work.
-  L and X, seal off the escape route. -  Copy, we're in through the back.
I'm curious.
How do you all commute to and from such a remote place like this?
There's a shuttle bus that runs between here and downtown every hour.
- Ah. -  Moving to the kitchen.
Okay.
Bale and Marco, report when you enter through the front.
Check. Moving in.
STATE GUEST HOUSE
Boss, it's not like I wanted anything big.
You said that when you retire, you'd pass this shitty nightclub to me.
Since the resort development's started, you've clammed up about our deal.
Tough guy.
You talk big for a little woodpecker chickenhawk motherfucker.
- Bitch-ass hoe. - What did you say?
Hey, kid. Nobody's gonna tell me when to retire, understood?
I'll do the deciding.
Oh? Let's do this, then.
You'll decide when I retire. I'll decide when you die, all right?
- Sound fair? - I'm getting the short end here.
No. I retire, and you die. That's only fair.
Someone bought a Tokarev from this site a few days ago.
They also bought a magazine with eight rounds.
When the information team dug deeper,
They discovered that there's going to be a turf war
Between the local gangs in that area in just a few days.
Take Bale, observe him. This will be his test run.
Sorry, we're not open today. You two can leave.
What?
- US military? - No, we're not. :cue
Man. You're pretty good at Korean.
If Bale follows orders well and cooperates, assign him to the team.
If he doesn't
Get rid of him.
Why the hell do they fight every damn day?
How come they can't get along like the both of us?
I know what you mean.
- Did you add water to this ramyeon? - Yeah, I did.
- You put so much that you can swim in it. - Hey, just eat it. Who cares?
Who are you?
This operation has to be staged to look like the local Korean gangs died
Fighting each other in a little turf war.
Refrain from using guns.
Guns are considered illegal in Korea anyway.
That sounds good to me.
One of the gangs has a Tokarev.
So be careful. Don't be reckless.
Hey, see? When gangsters get old,
You end up looking pathetic by trying to hold onto everything.
- Am I right? -  Yeah!
You're saying that in order to test Bale,
We're going into their turf war to kill all the gangsters?
Yes. Kill them all.
There shouldn't be any witnesses left.
This little punk the size of a woodpecker's dick
Couldn't do it by himself, so he dragged all his goons with him?
But I'm the "pathetic" one here?
Ding, dong, dang!
What the fuck is this about? I mean you setting a mood or what?
Is this the start of your retirement party?
Is this how your funeral party begins?
No, this is your retirement party.
You're gonna die at your funeral party.
Bang!
Wait, who are they? Turn it off!
What are those guys?
Ah, Korean yakuza guys are amusing.
But you've seen one, you've seen them all.
What the hell?
There are more of them than I expected.
Looks like it's going to take a little more time.
Oh shit, what's going on?
Did you call a multicultural band?
What a shit show, as expected from a little woodpecker dick.
- I thought you called them. - What?
Hey, who are you guys?
Some kind of boom-chick-a-boom dance troupe?
No, no. Look at that guy with the eye patch.
Those guys are a band.
Look up there. They're gonna boom-chick-a-boom. Look.
-  You're wrong. -  What?
They're an improv band.
Hey, turn off the music, asshole.
This is an interesting beat.
I told you to turn it off!
Did you hear me, you little shit?
You fucking dick.
What the fuck?
Light in front of death!
Light in front of death.
They call this an operation?
:cue
Bale! Move!
Why is Bale just standing around?
Hey, you fucking bastards!
What the hell are you?
This is a gun, you dance group motherfuckers!
Quicker than knives. If you don't want to die, stay still.
Fucking shitheads. Don't move.
Stay there. Don't come closer!
Fuck, I said stay there!
You motherfuckers.
Who the hell are you? Why are you doing this?
Where did you roaches come from? Do you want the nightclub?
Take the fucking nightclub. It's yours.
Say something, you fucking bastards.
Huh? Huh? Huh?
All clear.
No.
There's still one left.
You assholes.
You like to stab people right in the back, don't you?
Looks like I'm going to hell, without catching Jinman.
Hey, I might just take a few of you with me.
Hell? Count me out.
No, thanks.
I want to live a long, healthy life.
Marco. You never told us you speak Korean.
That's because nobody bothered to ask.
I'm a K-pop fan.
Abort the operation.
Some of you will get hurt if you keep going.
Teamwork clearly isn't in his vocabulary.
He's gotta go.
No. It would be such a waste.
We need Bale to capture Jeong Jinman.
Teamwork is more important than individual ability.
And there's too much risk.
That's a command.
Abort.
Did you really think you could force me out of the company by doing this?
Stop it!
Let's make this work. :cue
Oh, son, you're here?
-  Woojin, you're here. -  Come over here.
I brought this.
Take this bag with you and head home.
Sure, okay.
Everyone else, please take some when you leave.
I'll put them in front of the house.
Yeah, okay.
- Okay, got it. Got it. - Okay. Thank you.
I'll head home too, then.
Hey, hey.
- Take this with you and eat it. - No, it's okay. I don't really like fish.
It's not fish. Here, I'm giving you meat. Samgyeopsal.
I appreciate the meat.
Look at this girl. That was the key. You opened up with just that?
Why? Aren't things going well with our son?
Does he need a scolding? Clean up his act?
No, of course not.
- I am curious about something. - What is it? Go ahead, ask!
- I'll answer everything you want. -  Feel free to ask.
Why do you all call Mr. Woojin your son?
Cat got your tongue?
Tell the girl. She deserves to know.
Uh-huh, she's right. Why don't you sit?
Take a seat.
When Woojin was a little kid, his father died and his mother left.
His grandfather was really all he had.
But then his grandfather's boat capsized, and he died too.
After that, the people on the island all took turns raising
And looking after Woojin.
That's why he never left the island even though he should.
He's always right beside us, taking care of us like we did for him.
And so that's how Woojin became our island's "son."
- Hey, you're the same age, right? - Huh?
Why are you two so formal with each other?
"If you wouldn't mind. And thank you so much." Like that?
"Miss Arin, Mr. Woojin." You can't be serious.
It's cringy.
Just talk casually.
Um, please check it.
Here.
That's the ID and password for the app.
I got it from the captain,
But I'm not sure how the verification process works.
I tried it yesterday, but it blocked me out.
Have you eaten yet?
What?
The samgyeopsal
There's too much to eat by myself. :cue
Wanna eat together?
Uh
Oh, you go first.
Try it.
Auntie Jeomrye's meongge-jeot is really good with it.
Are you going to turn yourself in?
Yeah, I am.
Who's going to take care of the aunties' supplies when you're gone?
I'll keep it a secret.
Don't turn yourself in.
I appreciate that. Thank you so much, Miss Arin.
That's a load off.
I've been so worried about the aunties, I haven't been sleeping.
Just make sure that you don't get caught from now on.
Uh-huh.
Okay.
Well, since, um
You seem to know all of my secrets now,
How about you tell me one of yours?
- I'm curious about yours. - What?
That.
You don't have to tell me if it's uncomfortable.
I probably crossed the line. I apologize.
Someone might try to come and kill me.
I'm preparing for that.
My uncle taught me to defend myself since I was little.
That's why I run every day.
If someone comes after me, I can escape.
My parents died when I was pretty young,
And so my uncle was forced to raise me instead.
Hm. He did his best to raise me in his own way.
But I got scared so I ran away.
Why?
Is your uncle a scary person?
That's not what I meant.
My uncle's a good person, he's just bad at expressing himself.
That's all. I'll leave it at that.
Sure, yeah. I appreciate you sharing with me.
Should we talk more casually?
What?
The aunties said we're the same age.
I'm 22.
I'm 22, Miss Arin.
- Whoa - There's crumbs on your mouth, sir.
Go on, eat more. :cue
Yong, I hear there are more than 30 islands
Around here alone.
I don't think this is the way to find her.
First, we find the punk who took our stuff and disappeared.
Then next
We find this girl.
$2,000,000 DOLLAR/CASH JEONG JIAN BORN: FEBRUARY 11, 2003
-  Arin! -  Oh, my God!
What are you doing?
You said that you're scared.
I thought you'd be less scared if we ran together.
I didn't say I was scared.
SEASONED SQUID JEOTGAL I MADE IT. YOU ENJOY IT.
Even if there's soda in the South Sea,
You can't drink it if you don't have a cup.
Did I poke your side first, saying we should live together?
You kept poking first, saying we should live together!
Oh my, Arin knows how to laugh, after all?
Arin, you are so pretty when you smile.
Cute girl. Smile! Smile and live well.
You don't have to run with me to my house.
You have to go all the way back home.
It's all right. I enjoy doing it.
See you in the morning.
- Take this. - Keep it like that.
- Reel it in. - Hold tight.
You need to buy gochujang.
What else can I get you?
- How much is this? - Hi, Ma'am. It's 3,000.
-  Oh, Arin. -  What?
-  Hey, Woojin! Give Arin a ride. -  No, I'm working.
Get on, you're done, get outta here, get outta here.
Hold his waist real tight.
Go, have a good time.
Just be careful!
IT'S EXACTLY TO MY TASTE. I ENJOYED IT VERY MUCH - GRANDMA JEOMRYE
HANAM-DO ISLAND COMMUNITY UNITY FESTIVAL
:cue
Did you think we wouldn't find out that you sold our stuff somewhere else?
You disappeared.
No need to be afraid.
This girl.
I might forget about how you screwed me
If you tell me where to find her.
I envy you.
Why?
Even though you're not related,
You grew up with all the aunties and uncles all caring about you.
You're so loved.
I grew up living with my uncle.
But I never
It never felt like
I was loved.
Like I was always a burden to my uncle.
It just felt like that.
From my uncle's perspective, he could disappear any time,
So he wanted me to be able to survive on my own.
That's why he raised me to be tough.
Sometimes I understand.
But other times, I don't really want to.
The present is what counts now, right?
Hm?
The past is the past.
You came here and you've been loved ever since then.
A whole lot.
I mean, yeah.
I didn't realize at first,
But all the aunties have been so affectionate.
I didn't
Mean them.
I meant that you're being loved
By me.
:cue
Jeong Jian.
Who are you?
You ran away with our guns, didn't you?
There's the guy.
We tracked her down and now we get him as well.
It's killing two birds with one stone.
Let's take care of them quickly.
Woojin.
When I count to three,
Keep your head down, and run straight ahead.
- What? Straight ahead? - Three!
Woojin, get up, quick!
We can't kill her.
Arin!
FRONT TOWARD ENEMY
Arin
What is all this?
I'll explain everything later.
Shit.
Fucking bitch!
When I catch you,
I'll rip you to shreds.
Yong! Help me out here!
You're no ordinary bitch, are you?
It's all right, Woojin.
You little rats.
A SHOP FOR KILLERS 2
BASED ON THE NOVEL BY KANG JI YOUNG